Summary.

Current Site Reliability Engineer at start-up company Kasa. 7+ years experience specializing in the backend development, infrastructure automation, and computer hacking/security. Super nerd who loves Vim, Linux and OS X and enjoys to customize all of the development environment. Interested in devising a better problem-solving method for challenging tasks, and learning new technologies and tools if the need arises.

Experiencia

ASAC Asturias, España

Administrador de sistemas (practicas de empresa)

Feb.. 2021 - Mar. 2021

- Practicas de empresa en un Datacenter Tien 3. Trabajos con hardware especifico del servidor.
- Documentación de los procedimientos de actuación y trato con los clientes.

Universidad de Oviedo Oviedo, Asturias

BECARIO DE COLABORACIÓN DE SERVICIOS INFORMATICOS

Sep. 2019 - Jul. 2021

- Mantenimiento de los sistemas locales de la universidad.
- Clonación, instalación y actualización del hardware en equipos de la universidad.

Menciones y premios

VOLUNTARIOS

2021 **Finalista**, GameJam en el TechFest de la EII

Oviedo, España

Presentation

DevFest Seoul by Google Developer Group Korea

Seoul, S.Korea

PRESENTER FOR < HOSTING WEB APPLICATION FOR FREE UTILIZING GITHUB, NETLIFY AND CLOUDFLARE>

Nov. 2017

- · Introduced the history of web technology and the JAM stack which is for the modern web application development.
- Introduced how to freely host the web application with high performance utilizing global CDN services.

6th CodeEngn (Reverse Engineering Conference)

Seoul, S.Korea

PRESENTER FOR < DEFCON 20TH: THE WAY TO GO TO LAS VEGAS>

Jul. 2012

• Introduced CTF(Capture the Flag) hacking competition and advanced techniques and strategy for CTF

Presenter for <Metasploit 101>

S.Korea Sep. 2012

• Introduced basic procedure for penetration testing and how to use Metasploit

Writing

A Guide for Developers in Start-up

Facebook Page

Founder & Writer

Jan. 2015 - PRESENT

• Drafted daily news for developers in Korea about IT technologies, issues about start-up.

AhnLab

Undergraduate Student Reporter

6th Hacking Camp - S.Korea

Oct. 2012 - Jul. 2013

S.Korea

• Drafted reports about IT trends and Security issues on AhnLab Company magazine.

Program Committees _____

Educación

Universidad de Oviedo)

Oviedo, Asturias, España

Grado en Ingeniería Informática del Software

Sep. 2015 - Aug. 2021

• Sobresaliente en robótica aplicada

Conservatorio Superior de Música "Eduardo Martínez Torner

Oviedo, Asturias, España

Saxofonista

Sep. 2010 - Jun. 2016

Cambridge Assessment Oviedo, Asturias, España

B2 INGLES

Extracurricular Activity

B10S (B1t On the Security, Underground hacker team)

S.Korea

CORE MEMBER Nov. 2011 - PRESENT

- Gained expertise in penetration testing areas, especially targeted on web application and software.
- Participated on a lot of hacking competition and won a good award.
- Held several hacking competitions non-profit, just for fun.

WiseGuys (Hacking & Security research group)

S.Korea

MEMBER

Jun. 2012 - PRESENT

- Gained expertise in hardware hacking areas from penetration testing on several devices including wireless router, smartphone, CCTV and settop box.
- · Trained wannabe hacker about hacking technique from basic to advanced and ethics for white hackers by hosting annual Hacking Camp.

PoApper (Developers' Network of POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

CORE MEMBER & PRESIDENT AT 2013

Jun. 2010 - Jun. 2017

- · Reformed the society focusing on software engineering and building network on and off campus.
- Proposed various marketing and network activities to raise awareness.

PLUS (Laboratory for UNIX Security in POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

MEMBER

Sep. 2010 - Oct. 2011

- · Gained expertise in hacking & security areas, especially about internal of operating system based on UNIX and several exploit techniques.
- Participated on several hacking competition and won a good award.
- Conducted periodic security checks on overall IT system as a member of POSTECH CERT.
- Conducted penetration testing commissioned by national agency and corporation.

MSSA (Management Strategy Club of POSTECH)

Pohang, S.Korea

MEMBER

Sep. 2013 - Jun. 2017

- · Gained knowledge about several business field like Management, Strategy, Financial and marketing from group study.
- · Gained expertise in business strategy areas and inisght for various industry from weekly industry analysis session.